http://www.uniquevenues.com/privacy

Column 2
USA (cont.)
Column 3
USA (cont.)
Special Event Venues
Let us find a venue for you, free.Complete this form and we'll send your request to the venues that match your requirements, free.
Search for Venues
-- state/province/region --AlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinAlbertaBritish ColumbiaNew BrunswickNewfoundlandNorthwest TerritoriesNova ScotiaOntarioQuebecSaskatchewan
Find Venues for Me
Blog
Market Your Venue
Awards
Magazine
Webinars
Search for Venues
Find Venues for Me
Blog
Market Your Venue
Awards
Magazine
Webinars
You are here:
Home/Privacy/Terms Of Service & Use
Find a Venue
-- state/province/region --AlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinAlbertaBritish ColumbiaNew BrunswickNewfoundlandNorthwest TerritoriesNova ScotiaOntarioQuebecSaskatchewan
Privacy/Terms of Service & Use
Last Updated May 1, 2018
Privacy Statement
AMARC, Inc. (dba Unique Venues), respects your concerns about privacy. References in this Privacy Policy to “Unique Venues”, “we”, “us”, and “our” are references to the entity responsible for the processing of your personal information, which generally is the entity that obtains your personal information.
This Privacy Policy applies to the personal information we obtain through our websites, and social media pages (“Online Channels”); offline collection in connection with sales, marketing, and partners (“Offline Channels”); and third-party sources, including ad networks (collectively, the “Channels”).
This Privacy Policy describes the types of personal information we obtain through the Channels, how we may use that personal information, with whom we may share it, and how you may exercise your rights regarding our processing of the information. The Privacy Policy also describes the measures we take to safeguard the personal information we obtain and how you can contact us about our privacy practices.
The Online Channels may provide links to other third-party websites and features, or contain third-party cookies, that are not owned or controlled by Unique Venues. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of third parties, which are subject to their respective privacy policies.
Personal Information We Obtain
We may obtain personal information through the Channels. The types of personal information we may obtain include:
• Contact information (such as name, phone and fax number, email and postal address) for you;
• Information used to create your online account (such as username, password and security question and answer);
• Biographical and demographic information (such as venue name, event type and name, job title/position, detailed information about your venue and detailed information about your event);
• Purchase and customer service history;
• Financial information (such as payment information, including name, billing address and payment card details (i.e., card number, expiration date and security code); bank account information);
• Location data (such as data derived from your IP address, country and zip code) and the precise geolocation of your mobile device where we have provided notice and choice, as appropriate;
• Contact information you provide about other people you would like us to contact;
• Clickstream data and other information about your online activities (such as information about your devices, browsing actions and usage patterns), including across the Online Channels and third-party websites that we obtain through the use of cookies, web beacons and similar technologies;
• Other personal information contained in content you submit to us (such as through our Contact Us feature and Lead Forms).
We use third-party web analytics services in connection with the Online Channels, including Google Analytics, which uses cookies and similar technologies to collect data (such as IP addresses) to evaluate use of and interaction with the Online Channels. You may learn about Google’s advertising features, including Google Analytics’ currently available opt-out mechanisms by contacting Google.
Please note that providing personal information to us is voluntary on your part. If you choose not to provide us certain information, we may not be able to offer you certain products and services, and you may not be able to access certain features of the Online Channels.
Cookies and Similar Technologies
We use cookies, session variables and similar technologies on our Online Channels.
How We Use Personal Information
We may use the personal information we obtain to:
• Provide and administer our products and services;
• Process and fulfill orders and keep you informed about the status of your products and/or services;
• Communicate about and administer our products, services, events, programs and promotions (such as by sending alerts, promotional materials, newsletters and other marketing communications);
• Conduct and facilitate surveys, sweepstakes, contests, focus groups and market research initiatives;
• Perform data analytics (such as market research, trend analysis, financial analysis and customer segmentation);
• Engage in ad retargeting and evaluate the effectiveness of our marketing efforts (including through our participation in ad networks);
• Provide customer support;
• Process, evaluate and respond to requests, inquiries;
• Create, administer and communicate with you about your account (including any purchases and payments);
• Administer and register participants in our courses;
• Conduct marketing and sales activities (including generating leads, pursuing marketing prospects, performing market research, determining and managing the effectiveness of our advertising and marketing campaigns and managing our brand);
• Operate, evaluate and improve our business (such as by administering, enhancing and improving our products and services, developing new products, services and Online Channels, managing our communications and customer relationships, and performing accounting, auditing, billing, reconciliation and collection activities);
• Verify your identity and protect against and prevent fraud and other unlawful activity, unauthorized transactions, claims and other liabilities, and manage risk exposure and quality;
• Conduct investigations and comply with and enforce applicable legal requirements, relevant industry standards, contractual obligations and our policies and terms (such as this Privacy Policy and other Online Channels terms of use); and
• Maintain and enhance the safety and security of our products, services, Online Channels, network services, information resources and employees.
We may combine personal information we obtain through Online Channels with information we obtain through Offline Channels, as well as other information, for the purposes described above. We may anonymize or aggregate personal information and use it for the purposes described above and for other purposes to the extent permitted by applicable law. We also may use personal information for additional purposes that we identify at the time of collection. We will obtain your consent for these additional uses to the extent required by applicable law.
Personal Information Sharing
We do not sell or otherwise disclose personal information about you except as described here or at the time of collection.
• We may share personal information within Unique Venues for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy.
• We may share personal information with service providers we have retained to perform services on our behalf (such as payment processing, order fulfillment, customer support and data analytics). These service providers are contractually required to safeguard the information provided to them and are restricted from using or disclosing such information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or to comply with legal requirements.
• We may disclose personal information about you (1) if we are required or permitted to do so by applicable law or legal process (such as a court order or subpoena), (2) to law enforcement authorities or other government officials to comply with a legitimate legal request, (3) when we believe disclosure is necessary to prevent physical harm or financial loss, (4) to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights, (5) in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual fraud or illegal activity or, (6) otherwise with your consent.
• We reserve the right to transfer to relevant third-parties any information we have about you in the event of a potential or actual sale or transfer of all or a portion of our business or assets (including in the event of a merger, acquisition, joint venture, reorganization, divestiture, dissolution or liquidation) or other business combination. In such case, we will require the relevant third parties to provide comparable levels of protection as Unique Venues provides with respect to the information we share.
Your Choices
We offer you certain choices in connection with the personal information we obtain about you. To update your preferences, limit the communications you receive from us or submit a request, please contact us as specified in the How to Contact Us section of this Privacy Policy.
You also may exercise choice over how information about you and your venue by logging into your dashboard and updating any and all information about you and your venue.
How We Protect Personal Information Transmission
We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards, consistent with legal requirements where the personal information was obtained, designed to protect against unlawful or unauthorized destruction, loss, alteration, use or disclosure of, or access to, the personal information provided to us through the Channels.
Retention of Personal Information
To the extent permitted by applicable law, we retain personal information we obtain about you as long as (1) it is needed for the purposes for which we obtained it, in accordance with the provisions of this Privacy Policy or (2) we have another lawful basis, stated in this Privacy Policy or at the point of collection, for retaining that information beyond the period for which it is necessary to serve the original purpose for obtaining the personal information.
How to Contact Us
If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or if you would like us to update information we have about you or your preferences, please contact us:
239 Main Street, Suite 100
Johnstown, PA 15901
1-814-254-1310 phone
Todd Wonders, Technology
info@uniquevenues.com
Terms of Service
Company refers to Unique Venues and its assets including uniquevenues.com and uniquevenues.ca. Service, Site, Venue Content and Site Content refers to posts, uploads, videos, forms, layouts, menus, availability, pricing, etc.  Venues, Venue Managers, Venue Operators, Members, and Venue Owners refers to Unique Venues Clients and Customers. Planners, Event Planners, Groups refer to the End User of the Sites and its assets. Content can mean text, graphics, images, music, software, audio, video, information, works of authorship or other materials.
Event Planners
The Planner understands and agrees that Unique Venues and its Services bring together Venue Owners and Event Planners. Unique Venues is not a party to any agreements entered into between Venue Owners and Event Planners. Unique Venues has no control over the terms of any proposal generated by the Services, and the mere fact that Services allow Venue Owners to generate proposals with Unique Venues name and trademark listed on them shall in no way be interpreted as Unique Venues offering, condoning, guaranteeing or otherwise agreeing to be involved with the terms contained in any such proposal. Unique Venues expressly disclaims all liability in this regard.
Content on Site
Unique Venues services may be used and accessed for lawful purposes only. The following is prohibited:
Post, upload, publish, submit or transmit any content that: (i) infringes, misappropriates or violates a third party’s patent, copyright, trademark, trade secret, moral rights or other intellectual property rights, or rights of publicity or privacy; (ii) violates, or encourages any conduct that would violate, any applicable law or regulation or would give rise to civil liability; (iii) is fraudulent, false, misleading or deceptive; (iv) is defamatory, obscene, pornographic, vulgar or offensive; (v) promotes discrimination, bigotry, racism, hatred, harassment or harm against any individual or group; (vi) is violent or threatening or promotes violence or actions that are threatening to any other person; or (vii) promotes illegal or harmful activities or substances.
Use, display, mirror or frame Unique Venues site, or any individual element within the site including Unique Venues name, any Unique Venues trademark, logo or other proprietary information, or the layout and design of any page or form contained on a page, without Unique Venues express written consent;
Access, tamper with, or use non-public areas of the Services, or the technical delivery systems of Unique Venues providers;
Avoid, bypass, remove, deactivate, impair, descramble or otherwise circumvent any technological measure implemented by Unique Venues or any of Unique Venues providers or any other third party (including a Venue Owner/Manager or another Event Planner) to protect the services or Site Content;
Attempt to access or search the Site or Site Content or download Site Content from the Site through the use of any engine, software, tool, agent, device or mechanism (including spiders, robots, crawlers, data mining tools or the like) other than the software and/or search agents provided by Unique Venues or other generally available third party web browsers;
Send any unsolicited or unauthorized advertising, promotional materials, email, junk mail, spam, chain letters or other form of solicitation to Venue Owners/Managers using Site's Services and forms or other services and forms;
Use any meta tags or other hidden text or metadata utilizing Unique Venues trademark, logo URL or product name without Unique Venues express written consent;
Attempt to decipher, decompile, disassemble or reverse engineer any of the software used to provide the Services or Site Content;
Interfere with, or attempt to interfere with, the access of any Venue Managers or Owners, host or network, including, without limitation, sending a virus, overloading, flooding, spamming, or mail-bombing the Services;
Collect or store any personally identifiable information from the Services from Venue Owners or other users of the Services without their express permission;
Impersonate or misrepresent an affiliation with any person or entity;
Violate any applicable law or regulation; or
Encourage or enable any other individual to do any of the foregoing.
Unique Venues has the right to investigate and prosecute violations of any of the above to the fullest extent of the law. Unique Venues may involve and cooperate with law enforcement authorities in prosecuting those who violate these terms. Unique Venues reserves the right, at any time and without prior notice, to remove or disable access to any Content at its sole discretion, considers to be objectionable, in violation of these terms or otherwise harmful to the Services, Unique Venues and its Venue Owners and Operators.
Booking Venues
Event Planner expressly releases Unique Venues from any and all liability related to the booking, cancellation, payment, performance of a Venue, condition, or suitability of the Venue. Planner acknowledges and agrees that Unique Venues is not responsible for resolving any disputes between Venue Managers/Owners and Groups/Planners.
Disclaimer
Planner understands that Unique Venues does not screen or inquire into the background of any Venue Owners or other End User, nor does Unique Venues make any attempt to verify the statements of Venue Owners or End Users of Services. Unique Venues makes no representations or warranties to the conduct of Venue Owners or End Users.
Indemnity
Planner agrees to indemnify and hold harmless Unique Venues and its officers, directors, employees and agents, from and against any claims, disputes, demands, liabilities, damages, losses, and costs and expenses, including, without limitation, reasonable legal and accounting fees (including costs of defense of litigation by third parties), arising out of, or in any way connected with (a) Event Planner’s access to or use of the Services or Site Content or violation of these Terms; (b) Event Planner Content; and (c) Event Planner’s interaction with any Venue Owner or Manager, as applicable, including, but not limited to, (i) any condition caused by events beyond Unique Venues control that may cause damage to a Venue Owner’s Venue; and (ii) any injuries, losses, or damages (compensatory, direct, incidental, consequential or otherwise) of any kind arising in connection with or as a result of a booking or use of a Venue, or a Venue Owner’s listing of a Venue via the Services.
Venue Owners/Managers & Members
Venue Owners/Managers/Members understand and agree that Unique Venues and its Services bring together Venue Owners and Event Planners. Unique Venues is not a party to any agreements entered into between Venue Owners and Event Planners. Unique Venues has no control over the terms of any proposal or contract generated by the Services, and the mere fact that Services allow Venue Owners to generate proposals with Unique Venues name and trademark listed on them shall in no way be interpreted as Unique Venues offering, condoning, guaranteeing or otherwise agreeing to be involved with the terms contained in any such proposal. Unique Venues expressly disclaims all liability in this regard.
Becoming a Member
Venue Owner agrees to provide accurate, current and complete information during the sign-up process and to update such information to keep it accurate, current and complete during membership period.
Payment
Venue Owner/Manager understands that payment is due in full with membership application unless other terms have been agreed upon by Unique Venues.
Continuous Renewal
Venue Manager understands that membership is set up on continuous service unless otherwise noted. The continuous service program entitles Venue to uninterrupted service and access; membership will be automatically renewed at the end of each membership term (12 months, unless otherwise noted), at the rate(s) then in effect. Venue Manager/Owner permits authorization to charge credit/debit card if provided, or send invoice when applicable. Renewal notices will not be issued, instead, a clearly marked reminder notice will be sent to Venue Owner/Manager with the then current rate(s) about 30 days prior to charging the credit/debit card or issuing an invoice. The option to opt out of the continuous service program is available by accessing the member dashboard and indicating the choice to opt-out, no later than 2 months prior to the renewal date. Refunds will only be issued to cancellations received in writing within 7 business days from receipt of original Agreement or Renewal.
Errors and Omissions
Venue Manager/Owner is responsible for providing Unique Venues with display ad and/or all marketing materials by materials deadline date and assumes responsibility for quality of materials with regards to reproduction in print and online. In the event that Unique Venues fails to publish a display ad, or in the event that errors are made, liability to the venue shall be limited to refunding the cost of space actually occupied by the error or omission. Venue expressly waives and releases Unique Venues for any and all liability for actual error or consequential damages (including claims for lost profits or business).
Membership Benefits
Venue Owner/Manager is responsible for utilizing all benefits and services within marketing package. Unused benefits and services cannot be carried over to the following membership year.
Content on Site
Venue Owner agrees that Venue Owner is solely responsible for all venue profile content (including all images and text), copyright(s) and licenses pertaining to, and represents that the information is accurate. Unless otherwise explicitly stated herein or in the Privacy Policy, Venue Owner agrees that any Venue Owner Content provided in connection with this Site is provided on a non-proprietary and non-confidential basis. Venue Owner hereby grants to Unique Venues a non-exclusive, perpetual, irrevocable, royalty-free, fully paid-up, worldwide license (including the right to sublicense through multiple tiers) to use, reproduce, process, adapt, publicly perform, publicly display, modify, prepare derivative works, publish, transmit and distribute the Venue Owner Content, or any portion thereof, in any form, medium or distribution method now known or hereafter existing, known or developed, and authorize others to use the Venue Owner Content. Unique Venues may modify or adapt the Venue Owner Content in order to transmit, display or distribute such content over computer networks and in various media and/or make changes to the Venue Owner Content as necessary to conform and adapt such content to any requirements or limitations of any networks, devices, services or media.
Unique Venues services may be used and accessed for lawful purposes only. The following is prohibited:
Post, upload, publish, submit or transmit any content that: (i) infringes, misappropriates or violates a third party’s patent, copyright, trademark, trade secret, moral rights or other intellectual property rights, or rights of publicity or privacy; (ii) violates, or encourages any conduct that would violate, any applicable law or regulation or would give rise to civil liability; (iii) is fraudulent, false, misleading or deceptive; (iv) is defamatory, obscene, pornographic, vulgar or offensive; (v) promotes discrimination, bigotry, racism, hatred, harassment or harm against any individual or group; (vi) is violent or threatening or promotes violence or actions that are threatening to any other person; or (vii) promotes illegal or harmful activities or substances.
Use, display, mirror or frame Unique Venues site, or any individual element within the site including Unique Venues name, any Unique Venues trademark, logo or other proprietary information, or the layout and design of any page or form contained on a page, without Unique Venues express written consent;
Access, tamper with, or use non-public areas of the Services, or the technical delivery systems of Unique Venues providers;
Avoid, bypass, remove, deactivate, impair, descramble or otherwise circumvent any technological measure implemented by Unique Venues or any of Unique Venues providers or any other third party (including a Venue Owner/Manager or another Event Planner) to protect the Services or Site Content;
Attempt to access or search the Site or Site Content or download Site Content from the Site through the use of any engine, software, tool, agent, device or mechanism (including spiders, robots, crawlers, data mining tools or the like) other than the software and/or search agents provided by Unique Venues or other generally available third party web browsers;
Use any meta tags or other hidden text or metadata utilizing Unique Venues trademark, logo URL or product name without Unique Venues express written consent;
Attempt to decipher, decompile, disassemble or reverse engineer any of the software used to provide the Services or Site Content;
Interfere with, or attempt to interfere with, the access of any other Venue Managers or Owners or Event Planners, host or network, including, without limitation, sending a virus, overloading, flooding, spamming, or mail-bombing the Services;
Collect or store any personally identifiable information from the services of other Venue Owners or other End Users of the Services without their express permission;
Impersonate or misrepresent an affiliation with any person or entity;
Violate any applicable law or regulation; or
Encourage or enable any other individual to do any of the foregoing.
Unique Venues has the right to investigate and prosecute violations of any of the above to the fullest extent of the law. Unique Venues may involve and cooperate with law enforcement authorities in prosecuting those who violate these terms. Unique Venues reserves the right, at any time and without prior notice, to remove or disable access to any Content at its sole discretion, considers to be objectionable, in violation of these terms or otherwise harmful to the services, Unique Venues and its Venue Owners and Operators.
Bookings
Venue Owner expressly releases Unique Venues from any and all liability related to the booking, cancellation, payment, performance of Venue, performance of Group, suitability of the Venue. Venue acknowledges and agrees that Unique Venues is not responsible for resolving any disputes between Venue Managers/Owners and Groups/Planners.
Disclaimer
Venue Owner/Manager is solely responsible for all communication and interactions with Event Planners and other End Users of Services. Venue Owner understands that Unique Venues does not screen or inquire into the background of Event Planners, End Users and Groups, and makes no representations or warranties as to the conduct of Venue Owners/Managers and their Services.
Indemnity
Venue Owner/Manager agrees to indemnify, defend and hold harmless Unique Venues and its officers, directors, employees and agents, from and against any claims, disputes, demands, liabilities, damages, losses, and costs and expenses, including, without limitation, reasonable legal and accounting fees (including costs of defense of litigation by third parties), arising out of, or in any way connected with (a) Venues access to or use of the Services or Site Content or violation of these Terms; (b) Venues’ Content including images and videos with images that Venues post or request to be posted on their behalf; and (c) Venues interaction with any Event Planner or other End User, as applicable, including, but not limited to, (i) any condition caused by events beyond Unique Venues control that may cause damage to a Venue Owner’s Venue; and (ii) any injuries, losses, or damages (compensatory, direct, incidental, consequential or otherwise) of any kind arising in connection with or as a result of a booking or use of a Venue, or a Venue Owner’s listing of a Venue via the Services.
Digital Millennium Copyright Act
If you believe in good faith that any Venue Content or Site Content appearing on uniquevenues.com infringes your copyright, you may send a notice that the infringing content should be removed or access to it blocked. The notice must include the following information, as required by The Digital Millennium Copyright Act of 1998, ("DMCA") 17 U.S.C. Sec. 512:
A physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed;
Identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed (or if multiple copyrighted works located on MX.com are covered by a single notification, a representative list of such works);
Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing or to be the subject of infringing activity, and information reasonably sufficient to allow Medimetrix to locate the material;
The name, address, telephone number and email address (if available) of the complaining party;
A statement that the complaining party has a good-faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent or the law; and
A statement that the information in the notification is accurate and, under penalty of perjury, that the complaining party is authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.
Also, be aware that there may be penalties for false claims under the DMCA.
Our copyright agent may be reached at:
Charles Salem
AMARC Inc.
4169 Lower Park Drive
Fairfax, VA 22030
Phone: 8145251040
Email: chuck@uniquevenues.com
Talk to a Venue Specialist Make your party one-of-a-kind by finding the perfect party room for rent at Unique Venues.
Contact Us Today: Call us at the number below: 1-877-244-6110
Get help finding the perfect venue, we just need the details: Get Help Now
Speak to Venue Specialist:
1-877-244-6110
For general inquiries, please contact:
info@uniquevenues.com
OFFICES:
Contact us
Venue Log In
Username: *
Password: *
Forgot your password?
